<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Sultan Aloufi 🇸🇦</title><link>https://sultan-aloufi.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Sultan Aloufi 🇸🇦</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 16:19:32 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sultan-aloufi.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hooking Demystified</title><link>https://sultan-aloufi.github.io/posts/hello/hello/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 16:19:32 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://sultan-aloufi.github.io/posts/hello/hello/</guid><description>I have an application that I want to alter its behavior slightly to work for my specific use case, but I don&amp;rsquo;t have its source code. Can I alter its behavior while it&amp;rsquo;s running? Yes, by a technique called Hooking. It works by intercepting function calls or messages passed between programs. The code that handles the interception is called a hook.
So here is my challenge, I&amp;rsquo;ve to explain to you how function hooking works without any detail compromise.</description></item><item><title>Typing Sensitive Info, Check The URL First?</title><link>https://sultan-aloufi.github.io/posts/browser-in-browser-attack/bitb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 12:24:12 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://sultan-aloufi.github.io/posts/browser-in-browser-attack/bitb/</guid><description>Most of you check the url before typing any sensitive info to guarantee that info will be sent to the website you intended to. There is https://www.chase.com and there is https://www.chase.co/. You also check the padlock to insure the connection is encrypted so even if your internet traffic is being monitered, the data is encrypted so only you and chase.com know how to encrypt them. The middle man only knows you went to chase.</description></item><item><title>...</title><link>https://sultan-aloufi.github.io/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sultan-aloufi.github.io/projects/</guid><description>Coming soon ok, for now go take a run</description></item><item><title>Whoami</title><link>https://sultan-aloufi.github.io/aboutme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sultan-aloufi.github.io/aboutme/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m a Computer enthusiest who spends most time learning about computers and how they work. I mainly focus on Cybersecurity, Operating Systems, Networks, and Machine Learning Prjects/Research Dr. Luyi’s Security Research Team (Current)
Research and investigate a real-world cybercrime discovered by the team in 2019 on popular Android and iOS apps called Cross Library Data Harvesting (XLDH) Perform static and dynamic analysis on popular iOS and Android apps to detect malicious SKD’s integrated by the app for XLDH cases that stealthily steal user-sensitive data.</description></item></channel></rss>